HARSH WALIA

Gwalior, India | +91 9761423844 | harsh.p.walia@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/harsh-walia-32b968172/ | github.com/harshwalia36

SUMMARY

Data Science intern with a strong background in machine learning, deep learning, and NLP. Experienced in designing and building models for various applications. Achieved significant results in competitions and projects, demonstrating strong problem-solving skills and technical proficiency.

EXPERIENCE

SDE intern, Google India, Bangalore

Jan 2023 - July 2023

- Designed and Built a Multiple document summarization Engine from different Viewpoints by Fine-tuning different LLMs under Google Search Team
- Improved metrics by 2 percent and reduced...

SDE intern, SAMSUNG (SRI-B), Remote

May 2022 - July 2022

Data Science intern, INTERVIEW BIT (Scaler), Remote

Dec 2021 - April 2022

EDUCATION

Integrated BTech + Mtech, Information Technology, IIIT Gwalior

2018 - 2023

Gyankalash International School - 12th: Percentage 87% - 10th: CGPA 9.2/10

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Technical Skills: C (proficient), C++ (proficient), Python (proficient), SQL (proficient), JavaScript (familiar), Node.js (familiar), React.js (familiar), Flask (familiar), HTML (familiar), CSS (familiar), MongoDB (familiar)
- Frameworks/Libraries: Keras, TensorFlow, PyTorch, Sklearn, AWS, MLFlow, W&B, Numpy, Pandas, Matplotlib, Streamlit
- Domain Knowledge: Machine Learning, Deep Learning, NLP, Computer Vision, MLOps, Web Development
- Others: Git/Github, Heroku, Latex, Linux, openCV

LINKS

Github: harshwalia36 Leetcode: harshwalia (600+ solved) Geeks For Geeks: harsh_walia (200+ solved)

S